xtraorbit.com 2016-06-01

# XtraOrbit.Com :: Company Profile :: Privacy Policy :: Skrill, MoneyBookers, Perfect Money, PayPal, Payza, Egopay and Credit Cards Payments Accepted.

|  |  |   
---|---|---  
|  | 

|   
---  
**T** his Privacy Policy governs the manner in which XtraOrbit collects, uses, stores, archives and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of this Web site. Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.   
  
**The Information We Collect**

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the XtraOrbit website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive services. We may ask for personal information such as Name, Company Name, Address, Phone Number, Email Address and or Credit Card information.  

**The Way We Use This Information**

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. 

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. We will use information stored in our database about you to provide support. Email addresses and other data collected in support requests are not shared with outside parties unless you have consented as such to provide you with support. We may email directly to our customer lists special promotional offers from outside vendors, partners or suppliers. 

XtraOrbit uses aggregated, anonymous data for research regarding the effectiveness of the Web site and XtraOrbit’s marketing, advertising and sales efforts. XtraOrbit does not use such anonymous information for any other purpose. 

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.   

**Our Commitment To Data Security**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.  

**Our Commitment To Children's Privacy**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 18, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 18.   

**How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information**

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. We may disclose aggregated, anonymous data to investors and potential partners.   

**How To Contact Us**

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call send an email to privacy@xtraorbit.com.   

**Modification**

XtraOrbit reserves the right to add, delete, or modify any provision of its Privacy Policy at any time without notice.   

**XtraOrbit Team**  

|  |   

---  
|   
---|---  
  
---  
|   
You have a great way in dealing with problems, you are fair and your service is very fast.I'm enjoying it, and I hope we'll have a long business relationship.

Your service is just enthusiastic !!  
  
|    
**Fahad Jalali**  
Pakistan  

---  

Major payment methods are accepted, We accept major **credit** and **debit cards** , [**Perfect Money**](http://www.xtraorbit.com/web-hosting-and-domain-registration/pay-with/perfect-money.php), [**Egopay**](http://www.xtraorbit.com/web-hosting-and-domain-registration/pay-with/egopay.php), [**Paypal**](http://www.xtraorbit.com/web-hosting-and-domain-registration/pay-with/paypal.php), [**Skrill**](http://www.xtraorbit.com/web-hosting-and-domain-registration/pay-with/skrill.php), [**Moneybookers**](http://www.xtraorbit.com/web-hosting-and-domain-registration/pay-with/moneybookers.php), [**Payza**](http://www.xtraorbit.com/web-hosting-and-domain-registration/pay-with/payza.php), [**AlertPay**](http://www.xtraorbit.com/web-hosting-and-domain-registration/pay-with/alertpay.php) and **Google Checkout**.

So, you are free to order or register single domain names, bulk domain names, web hosting, cPanel hosting, website design and website templates Instantly using any of the above payment methods. 

---
